

KEMAL SENOVALI

GET IN CONTACT

Home: 004920238489128 Mobile: 017644409490

42277 Wuppertal, Collenbusch str 28

Website https://avilaweb.github.io/Kemal.gi thub.io/

PERSONAL PROFILE

Dedicated customer service professional with 10 years experience in a fast–paced environment seeking an opportunity in a team–orientated company. Adept at handling a wide range of contact methods while accurately documenting customer issues and providing first class service with every interaction.

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Russian Fluent
- · Bulgarian Native
- German Beginner
- Turkish Fluent

WORK EXPERIENCE

CCC DIGITAL GMBH - ESSEN (JUL 2018 - AUGUST 2020)

Content Moderator

Understanding client policies and guidelines, and making decisions based on them.

RUSCKOVETZ RESORT - 2777 DOBRINISCHTE (JAN 2017 - JUL 2018)

• Customer Service Manager Helping to build good customer relations Recruiting staff and doing appraisals Arranging staff meetings.

KFC, LONDON (Jan 2014 - Jan 2017)

• Customer Service Asst. Manager Delivering a comprehensive service to enquiring customers Managing a large number of incoming calls and emails

Hotel Melin - Tutrakan-Bulgaria (Jan 2012 - Jan 2014)

 Assistant Front Office Manager
Managing and motivating the Front Office team in order to provide a high standard of service for customers.

Four Points by Sheraton – Auckland – New Zealand (Jan 2010 – Jan 2012)

• Room Service Supervisor Supervising Room Service and Coffee Shop team and operational duties during Manager's absence.

HOTEL METROPOL , PRIMORSKO , BULGARIA (JAN 2006 - JAN 2010)

• Front Office Supervisor

Providing outstanding services and ensuring customer satisfaction. Addressing customer concerns and complaints promptly and professionally.

Safir Fintas Hotel - Kuwait

• Room Service Supervisor

Receiving orders via telephone and delivering food and beverage directly to guests' rooms Supervising Room Service and Coffee Shop team and operational duties during Manager's absence.

EDUCATION

• BACHELOR IN ECONOMY (MARKETING)